(Leonard:)The thing is, we've got this friend,
and he's kind of down in the dumps...
(Leonard:)...and we thought
maybe you could cheer him up.
(Raj:)With sex.
(Leonard:)I think she knows what I meant.
(Raj:)How can she
when you beat around the bush?
(Raj:)She's from the mean streets, where
they shoot from the hip and keep it real.
(Michaela:)Don't worry,
I can take good care of your friend.
(Leonard:)Okay, terrific. Um...
(Leonard:)Listen, is there a way that we can do this
where he doesn't know that you're a...
(Sheldon:)- You know...
- A prostitute.
(Michaela:)You want the girlfriend experience.
Yes, yes. Exactly.
The girlfriend experience.
(Raj:)Actually, if it's not too much to ask...
(Raj:)...could we have
the Jewish girlfriend experience?
(Sheldon:)Okay, that's question 20.
You have to guess.